Mental Health Association in New York State, Inc. (MHANYS) Records apap131
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Affiliates, 1957-2001; 5; 2 cubic ft.
  - Regional Mental Health Associations, 1957-1996; 5.1; 1.5 cubic ft.
    - Tompkins County, 1989-1993 (Box 2 (5-Affiliates), Folder 8)
    - Tompkins County, Newsletters, 1989-1992 (Box 2 (5-Affiliates), Folder 9)
    - Ulster County, 1989-1992 (Box 2 (5-Affiliates), Folder 10)
    - Warren and Washington Counties, 1987-1993 (Box 2 (5-Affiliates), Folder 11)
    - Westchester County, 1986-1994 (Box 2 (5-Affiliates), Folder 12)
  - Administration, 1959-2001; 5.2; 0.5 cubic ft.
    This subseries includes organizational information and information about the programs carried out by the local affiliates of MHANYS in New York state on the county and community level. Includes organizational information, correspondence, minutes of some local chapters' boards of directors, and feedback from the chapters to MHANYS on programs. Also includes affiliate guidelines and agreements records dealing with the creation of a regional mental health organization affiliated with MHANYS and NMHA and agreements between these affiliates and MHANYS regarding responsibilities and funding. The Affiliate Mail is an information exchange bulletin produced by MHANYS and sent to its affiliate chapters. The Public Information Project was carried out by MHANYS in 1985-1986 in connection with its local affiliates to increase public awareness of mental health issues. The Affiliate Survey was conducted by MHANYS of its local affiliates in order to develop an inventory that identifies present and future organizing activities and membership needs. The Staff Council folders include documents and correspondence relating to the meetings of the Staff Council, which was composed of the executive directors of local MHA chapters.
    - Affiliate List, 1978 (Box 2 (5-Affiliates), Folder 13)
    - Affiliate Mail, 1996 (Box 2 (5-Affiliates), Folder 14)
    - Affiliate Public Information Project, 1985-1986 (Box 2 (5-Affiliates), Folder 15)
    - Affiliate Public Information Project, 1985-1986 (Box 2 (5-Affiliates), Folder 16)
    - Affiliate Relations, 1972 (Box 2 (5-Affiliates), Folder 17)
    - Affiliate Relations, 1999 (Box 2 (5-Affiliates), Folder 18)
    - Affiliate Services Directory, 2000-2001 (Box 2 (5-Affiliates), Folder 19)
    - Affiliate Survey, 1996 (Box 2 (5-Affiliates), Folder 20-23)
    - Affiliation Agreements, 1994 (Box 2 (5-Affiliates), Folder 24)
    - Chapter Inquiries, 1978 (Box 2 (5-Affiliates), Folder 25)
    - Financial Issues, 1959-1961 (Box 2 (5-Affiliates), Folder 26)
    - Staff Council, 1991-1994 (Box 2 (5-Affiliates), Folder 27-28)
    - Summary, 1982 (Box 2 (5-Affiliates), Folder 29)
    - Why/How to Start an MHA, Undated (Box 2 (5-Affiliates), Folder 30)
- Advocacy, 1978-2002; 6; 3 cubic ft.
  The Advocacy series includes campaign packets, conference agendas and proceedings, presentations, testimony, meeting summaries and minutes, poll and survey results, publications, and other documentation of the efforts of MHANYS in the advocacy of positions regarding state and national policy on mental health and related issues, including state budgets, the Community Mental Health Resources Act of 1993, managed care, national health care programs, special needs plans, surrogate decision making, and other public issues.
  Arranged alphabetically by subseries.
  - Committees and Councils, 1989-2001; 6.1; 0.3 cubic ft.
    The mental health Committees and Councils subseries includes correspondence and other documents on the New York State Mental Health Services Council, an advisory council to New York State on mental health issues (Lucille Pritchard, executive director of MHANYS, was a member), advocacy material regarding national health care legislation, and minutes and other documents of subcommittees of the New York State Office of Mental Health dealing with Medicaid managed care.
    - Mental Health Services Council, 1989-1996 (Box 1 (6-Advocacy), Folder 1-2)
    - Mental Health Services Council, 1990 (Box 1 (6-Advocacy), Folder 3)
    - MHA Activities Kit, 1994 (Box 1 (6-Advocacy), Folder 4-5)
    - Mental Health Subcommittee, 1995 (Box 1 (6-Advocacy), Folder 6-7)
  - Friday Fax, 1997-2001; 6.2; 0.35 cubic ft.
    The Friday Fax was a weekly message sent out to the MHANYS's board, affiliates, and others regarding the current status of advocacy issues.
    - Friday Fax, 1997 (Box 1 (6-Advocacy), Folder 8)
    - Friday Fax, 1998 (Box 1 (6-Advocacy), Folder 9-10)
    - Friday Fax, 1999 (Box 1 (6-Advocacy), Folder 11-12)
    - Friday Fax, 2000 (Box 1 (6-Advocacy), Folder 13-15)
    - Friday Fax, 2001 (Box 1 (6-Advocacy), Folder 16-19)
    - Friday Fax, 2002 January-2002 March (Box 1 (6-Advocacy), Folder 20)
    - Friday Fax, 2002 April-2002 June (Box 1 (6-Advocacy), Folder 21)
    - Friday Fax, 2002 July-2002 September (Box 1 (6-Advocacy), Folder 22)
    - Friday Fax, 2002 October-2002 December (Box 1 (6-Advocacy), Folder 23)
    - Friday Fax, 2003 January-2003 March (Box 1 (6-Advocacy), Folder 24)
    - Friday Fax, 2003 April-2003 June (Box 1 (6-Advocacy), Folder 25)
  - Fundraising, 1999-2001; 6.3; 0.15 cubic ft.
    The Lawmakers Who Cook documents relate to an annual fundraising event sponsored by MHANYS to raise money for advocacy efforts.
    - Lawmakers Who Cook, 1999-2001 (Box 1 (6-Advocacy), Folder 26-32)
  - Issue Files, 1990-2001; 6.4; 1.2 cubic ft.
    The subseries includes material from a mental health advocacy campaign carried out by the Bazelon Center for Mental Health Law in Washington, DC. The managed care advocacy material relates to the place of mental health in managed care health plans and the organization of local task forces by MHANYS and its affiliates to address managed care issues. Also included are: Supplementary Security Income (SSI) eligibility standards for children with mental health and other disabilities; Special Needs Plans (SNP), which allow access by those with Serious Mental Illness (SMI) to SNPs under managed care; and the Vote Mental Health initiative which was a statewide voter mobilization and registration campaign.
    - Bazelon Center, Mental Health Campaign, 1994 (Box 2 (6-Advocacy), Folder 1-2)
    - Civil Commitment of Sexual Predators, 1997 (Box 2 (6-Advocacy), Folder 3)
    - Community Mental Health Resources Act, 1993 (Box 2 (6-Advocacy), Folder 4)
    - Congressional Candidates Poll, 1996 (Box 2 (6-Advocacy), Folder 5)
    - Correspondence with public officials and others, 1994 (Box 2 (6-Advocacy), Folder 6)
    - Fair Insurance Treatment (FIT) Act, 2001 (Box 2 (6-Advocacy), Folder 7)
    - Health Care Reform, 1993-1994 (Box 2 (6-Advocacy), Folder 8-10)
    - Health Care Reform, 1994 (Box 2 (6-Advocacy), Folder 11)
    - Integrated Systems Advocacy, 1997 (Box 2 (6-Advocacy), Folder 12-14)
    - Legislative advocacy for increased funding for community based system of care, 2001 (Box 2 (6-Advocacy), Folder 15)
    - Managed Care, 1995 (Box 2 (6-Advocacy), Folder 16)
    - Managed Care, 1996 (Box 2 (6-Advocacy), Folder 17-18)
    - Managed Care, 1996-1997 (Box 2 (6-Advocacy), Folder 19-20)
    - Managed Care, 1997-1998 (Box 2 (6-Advocacy), Folder 21)
    - Managed Care Task Force, 1997 (Box 2 (6-Advocacy), Folder 22-24)
    - May is Mental Health Month, 1994 (Box 2 (6-Advocacy), Folder 25)
    - Patients' Rights -- documents regarding state policy, 1997 (Box 2 (6-Advocacy), Folder 26)
    - Prior Approval -- Proposed New Part 551 regulations, 1998 (Box 2 (6-Advocacy), Folder 27)
    - Protection and Advocacy (PAIMI), 1995 (Box 2 (6-Advocacy), Folder 28)
    - Reinvestment Act, 1994 (Box 2 (6-Advocacy), Folder 29)
    - Rural Mental Health, 1989 (Box 2 (6-Advocacy), Folder 30)
    - Special Needs Plans (SNPs), 1996-1997 (Box 2 (6-Advocacy), Folder 31-35)
    - State Budget, 1990 (Box 2 (6-Advocacy), Folder 36)
    - State Budget, 1994-1995 (Box 2 (6-Advocacy), Folder 37-38)
    - Statewide Program Development -- Feasibility study aimed at enhancing the ability of MHANYS to meet the needs of people with mental illness, 1995 (Box 3 (6-Advocacy), Folder 1)
    - Supplementary Security Income (SSI), 1995-1996 (Box 3 (6-Advocacy), Folder 2-5)
    - Surrogate Decision Making, 1993 (Box 3 (6-Advocacy), Folder 6-7)
    - Vote Mental Health, 1992 (Box 3 (6-Advocacy), Folder 8-12)
  - Legislative Relations, 1978-2001; 6.5; 0.3 cubic ft.
    The Legislative Relations records relate to efforts of MHANYS to influence the New York State Legislature on issues related to mental health. Includes a newsletter from MHANYS on mental health issues, an annual MHANYS conference on mental health issues facing New York State legislature, records from the annual legislative day when mental health advocates from across the state assemble in Albany to hear presentations and visit the offices of state legislatures to lobby on behalf of a mental health issues agenda, legislative conferences and mini-conferences where mental health advocates discuss issues regarding current proposed legislation, and documents regarding MHANYS's Legislative Network of individuals donating to support of MHANYS advocacy and on a MHANYS mailing list for information on mental health policy issues. Also includes a bill paid by MHANYS to the Legislative Retrieval Service, an organization performing information retrieval services on legislation and supporting state records.
    - Legislative Alert Newsletter, 1993-1994 (Box 3 (6-Advocacy), Folder 13)
    - Legislative Conference, 1993-1998 (Box 3 (6-Advocacy), Folder 14)
    - Legislative Conference, 1997 (Box 3 (6-Advocacy), Folder 15)
    - Legislative Conference, 1999-2001 (Box 3 (6-Advocacy), Folder 16)
    - Legislative Day, 1996 (Box 3 (6-Advocacy), Folder 17)
    - Legislative Mini-Conference, 1994 (Box 3 (6-Advocacy), Folder 18-21)
    - Legislative Network, 1996 (Box 3 (6-Advocacy), Folder 22)
    - Legislative Network Donations, 1996 (Box 3 (6-Advocacy), Folder 23)
    - Legislative Program, 1998 (Box 3 (6-Advocacy), Folder 24-25)
    - Legislative Retrieval Service, 1991 (Box 3 (6-Advocacy), Folder 26)
    - Legislative Workshop, 1978 (Box 3 (6-Advocacy), Folder 27)
  - Position Papers, Alerts and Testimony Topics, 1992-1996; 6.6; 0.3 cubic ft.
    This subseries includes Education Rights of Children with Disabilities, Medicaid Managed Care, the Governor's Omnibus Bill, 1996-1997 state budget, reinvestment of savings from reductions in mental institution costs into mental health programs, voter registration, SSI, managed care, budget priorities, involuntary outpatient commitment, community mental Hygiene services, managed care, Clinton Health Care (Health Security) proposal, alternatives to promote recovery, children's mental health issues, outpatient restructuring, and other topics.
    - Position Papers, Alerts, 1996 (Box 3 (6-Advocacy), Folder 28-29)
    - Position Papers, Testimony, 1992-1999 (Box 3 (6-Advocacy), Folder 30-32)
    - Position Papers, Testimony, 1994 (Box 3 (6-Advocacy), Folder 33)
    - Public Hearing on Legislative Agenda, 1998 (Box 3 (6-Advocacy), Folder 34)
    - Public Hearing, 1999 (Box 3 (6-Advocacy), Folder 35-36)
    - Testimony -- alternatives to promote recovery, children's mental health issues, outpatient restructuring and other topics, 1990-1994 (Box 3 (6-Advocacy), Folder 37)
  - Press Releases, 1999-2002; 6.7; 0.2 cubic ft.
    Press Releases Press releases and media advisories, announcing MHANYS' activities, or expressing MHANYS' position on various legislative issues or other newsworthy events.
    - Press Releases and Media Advisories, 1999 January-1999 June (Box 3 (6-Advocacy), Folder 38)
    - Press Releases and Media Advisories, 1999 July-1999 December (Box 3 (6-Advocacy), Folder 39)
    - Press Releases and Media Advisories, 2000 January-2000 June (Box 3 (6-Advocacy), Folder 40)
    - Press Releases and Media Advisories, 2000 July-2000 December (Box 3 (6-Advocacy), Folder 41)
    - Press Releases and Media Advisories, 2001 January-2001 June (Box 3 (6-Advocacy), Folder 42)
    - Press Releases and Media Advisories, 2001 July-2001 December (Box 3 (6-Advocacy), Folder 43)
    - Press Releases and Media Advisories, 2002 January-2002 June (Box 3 (6-Advocacy), Folder 44)
    - Press Releases and Media Advisories, 2002 July-2002 December (Box 3 (6-Advocacy), Folder 45)
  - Training, 1993-1997; 6.8; 0.2 cubic ft.
    Advocacy Training Records from training programs to assist persons carrying out advocacy on behalf of mental health issues with New York State Government, including evaluation by participants of a training program on political advocacy carried out by MHANYS, and kits and documents to assist persons carrying out advocacy on mental health issues.
    - Advocacy Kit, 1994-1995 (Box 3 (6-Advocacy), Folder 46)
    - Advocacy Kit, 1996-1997 (Box 3 (6-Advocacy), Folder 47)
    - Advocacy Training, 1993 (Box 3 (6-Advocacy), Folder 48)
    - Advocacy Training, 1994 (Box 3 (6-Advocacy), Folder 49)
    - Advocacy Training, 1996 (Box 3 (6-Advocacy), Folder 50)
    - Advocacy Training, Evaluation, 1997 (Box 3 (6-Advocacy), Folder 51)
- Public Information, 1992-1998; 7; 0.5 cubic ft.
  The Public Information series includes appointment books of Eva Walter, MHANYS Director of Public Information; daybook of letters, faxes, memos and other documents sent and received by MHANYS Public Information Department; correspondence relating to requests to MHANYS for information on mental health issues; letter book of Eva Walters; phone log forms; and public information mailing lists. Other Public Information material includes literature on cultural diversity; correspondence with the New York Times and other media regarding news stories prepared with MHANYS assistance; forms for loans of MHANYS books, videos and other resources; correspondence with the Planet Earth Foundation, an organization producing media campaigns on public issues with whom MHANYS reviewed its programs; records of a MHANYS contract to distribute information on mental health issues; and correspondence and campaigns combating entertainment and other media that stigmatize people with mental health problems. The publication MHA Affiliate Mailing distributed information to MHANYS affiliates for their use in publicizing mental health issues on the local level.
  - Affiliate Mailing, 1993 (Box 1 (7-Public Information), Folder 1)
  - Affiliate Mailing, 1994 (Box 1 (7-Public Information), Folder 2-5)
  - Affiliate Mailing, 1995 (Box 1 (7-Public Information), Folder 6-11)
  - Affiliate Mailing, 1996 (Box 1 (7-Public Information), Folder 12)
  - Appointments, Eva Walters, 1992-1993 (Box 1 (7-Public Information), Folder 13)
  - Cultural Diversity, 1993 (Box 1 (7-Public Information), Folder 14)
  - Daybook, 1994 (Box 1 (7-Public Information), Folder 15-17)
  - Information Requests, 1991; 1993-1994 (Box 1 (7-Public Information), Folder 18)
  - Information Requests, 1997-1998 (Box 1 (7-Public Information), Folder 19)
  - Letter Book, 1995 (Box 1 (7-Public Information), Folder 20)
  - Mailing List, 1994 (Box 1 (7-Public Information), Folder 21-22)
  - Media Coverage, 1993 (Box 1 (7-Public Information), Folder 23)
  - Media Coverage, Undated (Box 1 (7-Public Information), Folder 24)
  - Mental Health Resources Center forms, 1995 (Box 1 (7-Public Information), Folder 25)
  - Phone Log, 1994 January-1994 June (Box 1 (7-Public Information), Folder 26)
  - Phone Log, 1994 July-1994 December (Box 1 (7-Public Information), Folder 27)
  - Phone Log, 1995 January-1995 June (Box 1 (7-Public Information), Folder 28)
  - Phone Log, 1995 July-1995 December (Box 1 (7-Public Information), Folder 29)
  - Planet Earth Foundation, 1994 (Box 1 (7-Public Information), Folder 30)
  - Public Information and Education Program, 1985 (Box 1 (7-Public Information), Folder 31)
  - Public Education Program, 1993 (Box 1 (7-Public Information), Folder 32)
  - Publicity Materials, 1981-1985 (Box 1 (7-Public Information), Folder 33-34)
  - Stigma, 1995 (Box 1 (7-Public Information), Folder 35)
  - Video -- correspondence with video producers, 1994 (Box 1 (7-Public Information), Folder 36)
- Community Mental Health Promotion Project, 1987-2002; 8; 1.5 cubic ft.
  This series deals with a contract obtained by MHANYS from the New York State Office of Mental Health in 1995 to establish community mental health promotion teams in twelve areas of New York State. The project files include material from Community Mental Health Promotion Project collected and maintained by Darlene Ward, which were reclassified from working files to archival material in February 2001. These files are arranged in their original order followed by the publication Community Connections and project administrative files. Community Connections was a quarterly newsletter publication of the Community Mental Health Promotion Project providing information on mental health issues. The publication was known as MHANYS Connections until 1994 with the title changing to Community Connections in 1995. The administrative records folders include correspondence, conference documents, program proposals.
  - Managed Care, 1997 (Box 1 (8-Community Mental Health Promotion Project), Folder 1)
  - Welfare Reform, 1997 (Box 1 (8-Community Mental Health Promotion Project), Folder 2)
  - Medicaid, 1997 (Box 1 (8-Community Mental Health Promotion Project), Folder 3)
  - Defining Consumer, 1997 (Box 1 (8-Community Mental Health Promotion Project), Folder 4)
  - Prior Authorization, Drug, 1997 (Box 1 (8-Community Mental Health Promotion Project), Folder 5)
  - Empowerment, 1995 (Box 1 (8-Community Mental Health Promotion Project), Folder 6)
  - Reinvestment, 1997 (Box 1 (8-Community Mental Health Promotion Project), Folder 7)
  - Parental Rights, 1997 (Box 1 (8-Community Mental Health Promotion Project), Folder 8)
  - Medicaid Managed Health, 1997 (Box 1 (8-Community Mental Health Promotion Project), Folder 9)
  - Health Care Reform Activities Kit, 1994 (Box 1 (8-Community Mental Health Promotion Project), Folder 10-11)
  - Parity, 1996 (Box 1 (8-Community Mental Health Promotion Project), Folder 12)
  - Involuntary Commitment, 1993 (Box 1 (8-Community Mental Health Promotion Project), Folder 13-14)
  - Civil Commitment, 1991 (Box 1 (8-Community Mental Health Promotion Project), Folder 15-16)
  - Financial Package for Mentally Ill, 1992 (Box 1 (8-Community Mental Health Promotion Project), Folder 17)
  - Housing Plan, 1996 (Box 1 (8-Community Mental Health Promotion Project), Folder 18)
  - Mental Hygiene Law Amendment, 1991 (Box 1 (8-Community Mental Health Promotion Project), Folder 19)
  - Home Relief, 1992 (Box 1 (8-Community Mental Health Promotion Project), Folder 20)
  - Homelessness, 1991 (Box 1 (8-Community Mental Health Promotion Project), Folder 21)
  - Involuntary Commitment, 1994 (Box 1 (8-Community Mental Health Promotion Project), Folder 22)
  - Comprehensive Outpatient Program Funding, 1998 (Box 1 (8-Community Mental Health Promotion Project), Folder 23)
  - Discharge Planning, 1996 (Box 1 (8-Community Mental Health Promotion Project), Folder 24)
  - Forensics -Mentally Ill- Justice System, 1996 (Box 1 (8-Community Mental Health Promotion Project), Folder 25)
  - Seclusion and Restraint, 1998 (Box 1 (8-Community Mental Health Promotion Project), Folder 26)
  - Juvenile Justice System, 1998 (Box 1 (8-Community Mental Health Promotion Project), Folder 27-29)
  - Justice for Juveniles - Community Assessment, 1998 (Box 1 (8-Community Mental Health Promotion Project), Folder 30)
  - Juvenile Justice Assessment, 1998 (Box 1 (8-Community Mental Health Promotion Project), Folder 31)
  - Justice for Juveniles, 1998 (Box 1 (8-Community Mental Health Promotion Project), Folder 32)
  - Juvenile Justice -- GAINS, 1998 (Box 1 (8-Community Mental Health Promotion Project), Folder 33)
  - Juvenile Justice, 1998-1999 (Box 1 (8-Community Mental Health Promotion Project), Folder 34)
  - Juvenile Justice -- Families, 1999 (Box 1 (8-Community Mental Health Promotion Project), Folder 35)
  - Justice for Juveniles Forum, 1999 (Box 1 (8-Community Mental Health Promotion Project), Folder 36-38)
  - Youth MICA Resource Center, 1999 (Box 1 (8-Community Mental Health Promotion Project), Folder 39)
  - Juvenile Justice Legislation, 1999 (Box 1 (8-Community Mental Health Promotion Project), Folder 40)
  - Juvenile Justice RFP, 1999 (Box 1 (8-Community Mental Health Promotion Project), Folder 41)
  - Adolescent Depression Campaign, 1998 (Box 1 (8-Community Mental Health Promotion Project), Folder 42-43)
  - Parity Article - Glazier, 1998 (Box 1 (8-Community Mental Health Promotion Project), Folder 44)
  - Prevention Conference, 1998 (Box 1 (8-Community Mental Health Promotion Project), Folder 45)
  - Dual Recovery, 1998 (Box 1 (8-Community Mental Health Promotion Project), Folder 46)
  - Business Outreach, 1997 (Box 1 (8-Community Mental Health Promotion Project), Folder 47)
  - Parental Rights, 1998 (Box 1 (8-Community Mental Health Promotion Project), Folder 48)
  - Adolescent Depression, 1998 (Box 1 (8-Community Mental Health Promotion Project), Folder 49-50)
  - Adolescent Depression Survey, 1998 (Box 1 (8-Community Mental Health Promotion Project), Folder 51)
  - Justice for Juveniles Forum, 1999 (Box 1 (8-Community Mental Health Promotion Project), Folder 52)
  - Juvenile Justice, 1999 (Box 1 (8-Community Mental Health Promotion Project), Folder 53)
  - Depression - School partnerships, 1998-1999 (Box 1 (8-Community Mental Health Promotion Project), Folder 54)
  - Adolescent Depression, 1998 (Box 1 (8-Community Mental Health Promotion Project), Folder 55-57)
  - Managed Care, 1997 (Box 1 (8-Community Mental Health Promotion Project), Folder 58)
  - Children's Mental Health, 1996 (Box 2 (8-Community Mental Health Promotion Project), Folder 1-4)
  - Children's Mental Health, 1997 (Box 2 (8-Community Mental Health Promotion Project), Folder 5)
  - Children's Mental Health Teleconference, 1998 (Box 2 (8-Community Mental Health Promotion Project), Folder 6-7)
  - Children's Special Needs, 1998 (Box 2 (8-Community Mental Health Promotion Project), Folder 8)
  - Children's Issues, 1998 (Box 2 (8-Community Mental Health Promotion Project), Folder 9-10)
  - Child Health Insurance, 1997 (Box 2 (8-Community Mental Health Promotion Project), Folder 11)
  - Child Health Insurance, 1998-1999 (Box 2 (8-Community Mental Health Promotion Project), Folder 12)
  - Parity, 1997 (Box 2 (8-Community Mental Health Promotion Project), Folder 13-14)
  - Legislative Alerts, 1996 (Box 2 (8-Community Mental Health Promotion Project), Folder 15)
  - Parent and Family Issues, 1995 (Box 2 (8-Community Mental Health Promotion Project), Folder 16)
  - Parents with Psychiatric Disabilities (PPD), 1998 (Box 2 (8-Community Mental Health Promotion Project), Folder 17-18)
  - Advocacy not elsewhere classified, 1993-1997 (Box 2 (8-Community Mental Health Promotion Project), Folder 19)
  - MHANYS Connections, 1987-1989 (Box 2 (8-Community Mental Health Promotion Project), Folder 20)
  - MHANYS Connections, 1990-1994 (Box 2 (8-Community Mental Health Promotion Project), Folder 21)
  - Community Connections, 1995-1998 (Box 2 (8-Community Mental Health Promotion Project), Folder 22)
  - Community Connections, 1999-2002 (Box 2 (8-Community Mental Health Promotion Project), Folder 23)
  - Community Mental Health Promotion Project, Administrative Records, 1996 (Box 2 (8-Community Mental Health Promotion Project), Folder 24-26)
- Depression Awareness, Recognition and Treatment (D/ART), 1988-1998; 9; 0.5 cubic ft.